apotelyt.com 2019-04-13

# Privacy Policy

Your **privacy is valued** and the importance of protecting your personal data is recognized. This notice describes the privacy policy of APOTELYT.COM ("the Site") and the treatment of personal information. By visiting the Site, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy Notice. 

Any personal details you submit to the Site, such as your name and email address, will not be used for any other purposes than to contact you in case a message from you requires a reply. The Site will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to **prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information**. The Site will securely store any personal information you provide and will not sell it or pass it on to others. 

##  First-party cookies 

The Site receives and stores certain types of non-personal information whenever you interact with it. Like many other websites, the Site uses " **cookies** " to save selected data about your internet session, such as IP address and referring page. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are stored by your Web browser and enable the provision of personalised site features. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its producer. However, because cookies may allow you to take advantage of some of the Site's essential features, it is recommended that you leave them turned on.

## Third-party cookies

Like many other websites, the Site uses **Google Analytics** to monitor and analyse internet traffic. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use, which are stored via cookies on client computers. The information thereby generated is used to create reports that are of interest to webmasters. For example, data about the frequency of visits to the website, the particular pages viewed, and the platform used is collected. These data make it possible to improve a website's design and better tailor its contents to visitor customs and preferences. Google will store and use this information in line with the [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). If you would like to opt out of Analytics cookies, you can do so by [installing a respective plug-in](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) to your browser. 

The Site publishes **Google Adsense** advertisements, which are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine the latter, Google will track your behaviour across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using [Google's ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences). You can also completely opt-out of receiving the Adsense partner network cookie. However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser, your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you might want to use a respective [Google browser plug-in](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin). 

The Site contains plug-ins for the social network **Facebook**. You will recognise Facebook plug-ins by the Facebook logo on the Site. If you click the Facebook "Like" button while you are signed in to your Facebook account, you can link the content of the Site to your Facebook profile. This means that Facebook can allocate this interaction with the Site to your user account. The Site does not receive any notification about the content of the conveyed data or how it is used by Facebook. Further information about this topic can be found in the [Facebook data privacy statement](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php). If you do not want Facebook to be able to allocate your use of the Site to your Facebook user account, please do not click on the "Like" button or sign out of your Facebook account.

The Site uses the Plus One interface provided by the social network **Google Plus** , which is operated by Google. If you do not click on the button, no personal data will be captured. Data, including the IP address, is only captured and processed from members who are signed in to their account. Information about the purpose and extent of capturing this data and the further processing and use of the data by Google as well as your respective rights and options to protect your personal privacy can be found in [Google’s data privacy notifications](http://www.google.com/intl/de/+/policy/+1button.html) about the Plus One button, as well as in [Google’s data privacy policies](https://www.google.com/intl/de/policies/privacy). If you are a Google Plus member and do not want Google to collect data about you via the Site, you should sign out of your Google Plus account.

Some functions offered by the online news and social networking service **Twitter** are integrated into this Site. Using Twitter and the function called "Tweet" enables websites that you have visited to be linked to your Twitter account and made available to other users. In the process, data is conveyed to Twitter that might be used for the purpose of conversion tracking and serving targeted ads. The Site does not obtain any knowledge about the content of the conveyed data or how it is used by Twitter. You can find more information about the treatment of personal information in the [Twitter data privacy statement](http://twitter.com/privacy). Moreover, you can change your privacy preferences by visiting and updating the account-specific [data privacy settings](http://twitter.com/account/settings) on the Twitter website. 

## Notices and revisions

If you have any concern about privacy at this Site, please send an email to the editor with a thorough description, so that we can resolve the issue. As the Site changes frequently, this Privacy Policy Notice might also undergo alterations, so please check back periodically in order to be informed of any updates. The **most recent privacy policy applies** to all information that the Site has about you. However, the Site will never materially change its policies and practices to make them less protective of user information collected in the past without the consent of affected users. 

## Last Update

The information on this page was last updated on 31 October 2016.
